Autograph File, B: Guide.
Autograph File, B,
- Bryce, James Bryce, viscount, 1838-1922. A.L.s. to [Sir George Granville] Leveson-Gower; [London] 15 Dec 1899., 1s.(2p.)
  *43M-197. Purchased with the Sheldon fund from Mrs. Russell Law, 27 Oct 1943.
- Bryce, James Bryce, viscount, 1838-1922. A.L.s. to [Thomas Nast]; [London] 2 Feb 1895., 1s.(4p.)
- Bryce, James Bryce, viscount, 1838-1922. A.L.s. to Charles Dudley Warner; [London] 3 Jul [1891], 1s.(1p.) env.
- [Bryce, James Bryce, viscount, 1838-1922] [Survey of southeastern Europe] TS.(unsigned, with autograph revisions); [Williamstown, Mass., n.d.], 3s.(3p.)
  Pages 4,15,18 only of a longer TS.
  *41-6181. Gift of Mrs.Gamaliel Bradford, 27 May 1942.
- Byrd, Richard Evelyn, 1888-1957. T.L.s. to Frederic Henri Viaux; Boston, 9 Oct 1933., 1s.(1p.)
  *69M-15. Gift of Frederic B. Viaux and Florence Viaux, Dec 1969.
- Brydges, Sir Samuel Egerton, 1762-1837. A.L.s. to T. B. Brydges Barrett; Geneva, 24 Jun 1831., 1s.(4p.)
  Includes a long political letter addressed "To the worthy freeholders of the county of Kent."
  *62M-37. Purchased with the Wells fund, 17 Sept 1962.
- Brydges, Sir Samuel Egerton, 1762-1837. A.L.s.to Messrs Brall; Plomet; [Canterbury] 19 Feb 1809., 1s.(1p.)
- Brydges, Sir Samuel Egerton,bart.,1762-1837. A.L.s. to [William Pickering?]; Geneva, 27 Mar 1832., 1s.(4p.)
  *56M-23. Purchased with the Greenough fund from Peter Murray Hill Ltd., Sept 1956.
- Buccleuch, Duchess of M. House, Saturday
  To Mr. Atkinson
- Buccleuch, Henry Scott, 3d duke, 1746-1812. A.signature; Selkirk, 7 Nov 1816. Also a.signature of Charles William Henry, 4th duke Buccleuch (1774-1819); Edinburgh, 10 Jun 1799., 1s.(1p.)
- Bucham, Ida Whipple Mystic Bridge, Ct. Ms. poem "Frost and the Flowers".
- Buchan, David Stewart Erskine, 11th earl of, 1742-1829. A.L.s.to Alexander Nasmyth; Drybergh Abbey, 3 Aug 1820., 1s.(1p.)
- Buchan, David Stewart Erskine, 11th earl of, 1742-1829. A.L.(3d person) to Rejoice Newton; Drybergh Abbey, 11 Aug 1817., 1s.(1p.)
- Buchanan, James, 1791-1868. A.L.s. to Rollin Abell; Washington, 8 Aug 1848., 1s.(2p.)
- Buchanan, James, pres. U. S., 1791-1868. A.L.s. to [George] Bancroft; [Washington, 14 May 1845], 1s.(1p.)
  *42M-499(22). Gift of Dr. Harris Kennedy, 26 Jan 1943.
- Buchanan, James, pres.U.S., 1791-1868. A.L.s.to James Campbell; Lancaster, 5 Feb 1851., 1s.(1p.)
- Buchanan, James, pres.U.S., 1791-1868. 2 A.L.s.to Stephen Pleasonton:
  - London, 13 Jan 1853., 1s.(4p.)
  - St. Petersburg, 6 Jul 1832., 1s.(4p.)
- Buchanan, James, pres.U.S., 1791-1868. A.L.s.to Theodore Sedgwick; London, 27 Mar 1855., 1s.(1p.)
- Buchanan, James, pres. U.S., 1791-1868. MS.D.s.; Executive Mansion, 2 Mar 1861., 1s.(2p.)
  *81M-44. Gift of Barbara Newman Kravitz '52, Feb 1982.
- Buchanan, James, pres.U.S., 1791-1868. Printed document, s.; New Bedford, 20 May 1841., 1s.(1p.)
  Shipping papers for a whaling ship bound for the Pacific.
- Buchanan, Robert, 1785-1873. A.L.s. to Trubner; [London] 27 Feb 1880., 1s.(3p.)
  *54M-179. Purchased from Robert K. Black, 7 Feb 1955.
- Buchanan, Robert, 1841-1901. A.L.s. to T K Chambers; Oban [Argyllshire] 5 Jun 1870., 1s.(3p.)
  *46M-400. Bequest of Evert Jansen Wendell, 1918.
- Buchanan, Scott Milross, 1895-1968. The liberal college in the world: typescript with autograph manuscript corrections, Chicago (Ill.),1942 May 8., 1 folder
  *96M-15. Gift of Stephen Benedict, 1996 Oct. 16.
- Buckalew, Charles Rollin, 1821-1899. 3 A. signatures; [n.p.] 1867., 1s.(1p.)
- Buckingham London, July 16, 1881
  To ?
- Buck, Pearl (Sydenstricker) 1892- T.L.s.to John Cournos; Perkasie, 12 Jun 1941., 2s.(2p.) env.
  *59M-85. Purchased with the E. A. Wells fund from John Cournos, 17 Sept 1959.
- Buck, Pearl (Sydenstricker) 1892- Letters to Frank T. Kauffman:
  - T.L.s.; Perkasie, Penna; 28 Jan 1943., 1s.(1p.) env.
  - T.L.s.; Perkasie, 11 Dec 1950., 1s.(1p.) env.
    *53M-155. Purchased from Frank T. Kauffman, June 1954.
- Buck, Pearl (Sydenstricker) 1892- T.L.s.to editor, New York Sun; Perkasie, 4 Jun 1941., 2s.(2p.)
  *59M-84. Purchased with the E. A. Wells fund from John Cournos, 17 Sept 1959.
- Buckingham, James Silk, 1786-1855. A.L.s. to [ ]; [London] 30 Apr 1845., 1s.(1p.)
  r.f. x5.15F
  Gift of Norton Perkins, 1928.
- Buckingham, Joseph Tinker, 1779-1861. A.L.s. to Messrs. Bolles and Houghton; Cambridge, 11 Feb 1852., 1s.(2p.)
- Buckingham, Joseph Tinker, 1779-1861. A.L.s. to [ ] Bryce; Washington, 20 Mar 1828., 1s.(2p.)
  *42M-1951. Presented by the Estate of Samuel Henshaw. Gift of Thomas Barbour and others, June 1942.
- Buckingham, William Alfred, 1804-1875. A.L.s.to [Mrs ] Gardner; Norwich, 9 Jun 1866., 1s.(1p.)
- Buckingham, William Alfred, 1804-1875. A. signature; Norwich, Ct., 18 Feb 1867., 1s.(1p.)
- Buckland, Francis Trevelyan, 1826-1880. A.L.s. to [ ]; [n.p.] 22 May 1849., 1s.(2p.)
  *47M-373 (15). From the estate of Samuel Henshaw. Gift of Mr. and Mrs. Alfred M. Tozzer,; Mrs. Thomas Barbour, and Miss Gertrude A. Thurston, June 1943.
- Buckland, William, 1784-1856. A.L.s.to George Ticknor; [n.p.] 3 Jul 1835., 1s.(1p.)
- Buckland, William, 1784-1856. A.L.s.to [ ] Coleman; Oxford, 10 May 1844., 1s.(2p.)
- Buckle, Henry Thomas, 1821-1862. A.L.s.to [ ]; London, 31 Mar 1859., 1s.(3p.)
  Removed from TP 1905.6.30.
- Buckminster, Joseph Stevens, 1784-1812. A.L.s.to William Smith Shaw; Cambridge, 17 May 1799., 1s.(3p.)
- Buckner, Simon Bolivar, 1886-1945. A.L.s. to Lee Max Friedman; [Okinawa] 4 May 1945., 3s.(3p.)
  *45M-432. Gift of Lee M. Friedman, 18 Aug 1945.
- Buckner, Simon Bolivar, 1823-1914. A.signature; [n.p.] 14 Nov 1896., 1s.(1p.)
- Bucknill, T[homas] T[ownsend], Sir, 1845-1915. ALs (reproduction) with AMs insertions to S. Lambert; Epsom (England),1899 Jan. 9., 1s.(1p.)
  *93M-218. No source or date.
- Buckstone, John Baldwin, 1802-1879. A.L.s.to [ ]; Liverpool [n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Buddecke, P. W. German Legation Washington, March 28, 1887
  To Ben. W. Austin
- Budiner, Melitta. Einige Daten über Kindheit und Jugend von Herbert Steiner. TS. (unsigned); [n.p., 1976], 2s.(3p.)
  Gift of Walter Grossman, 1976.
- Budington, William Ives, 1815-1879. A.L.s.to Mrs A. H. Foote; Brooklyn, 21 Oct 1862., 2s.(7p.)
- Buel, C. C. Autograph
  American editor.
- Buell, Don Carlos, 1818-1898. A.L.s. to John Earle Jr. Co.; St. Louis, 2 Oct 1849., 1s.(1p.)
  *45M-181(79). Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Buell, Horatio Gates. 10 A.L.s. to Sarah Josepha (Buell) Hale; [v.p.] 1809-1824., 10s. (35p.)
  *46M-210F. Anonymous donor, 25 July 1946.
- Buell, Horatio Gates. MS.D.s.; Newport, 24 Oct 1810., 1s.(3p.)
  *46M-210. Anonymous donor, 25 July 1946.
- Buffon, Georges Louis Leclerc, comte de, 1707-1788. A.L.s.to [ ] de Beaumont; [Paris] 1 Jan 1775., 1s.(2p.)
  *43M-168. Transferred from the Museum of Comparative Zoology, 30 Sept 1943.
- Buffon, Georges Louis Leclerc, comte de, 1707-1788. A.L.(unsigned) to [Philibert] Guéneau de Montbeillard; [n.p.] 20 Jan [17--], 1s.(3p.)
  *57M-132. Gift of David P. Wheatland, purchased from Charavay, Dec 1957.
- Buffon, Georges Louis Leclerc, comte de, 1707-1788. MS.L.s.to [ ]; Mouthard, 3 Mar 1777., 1s.(2p.)
  *57M-97. Deposited by George Benson Weston, 27 Dec 1957. Later bequest.
- Buffon, Georges Louis Leclerc, comte de, 1707-1788. A.L.s.to [ ]; Montbard[?] 24 Feb 1783., 1s.(2p.)
- Buffon, Georges Louis Leclerc, comte de, 1707-1788. A.L.s.to [ ]; [n.p.] 22 Apr [n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Buffon, Georges Louis Leclerc, comte de, 1707-1788. A. signature (Buffon 1737 ); [n.p.] 1737., 1s.(1p.)
  *45M-181(80). Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Buffum, Arnold, 1782-1859. A.L.s. to Elizabeth (Buffum) Chace; Perth Amboy, N.J., 14 May 1856., 1s. (2p.)
  Recat. fr. MS Am 5008.
  Purchased with the Jackson fund, 8 June 1938.
- Buhre, Paul St. Petersburg, February 11, 1884
  Consul des S. U. de Venezuela.
- Bukett, John. A.L.s. to John Charles Fremont; Brooklyn, 22 Nov 1856., 1s.(2p.)
- Bulfinch, Charles, 1763-1844. A.L.s. to [Samuel?] Bradlee; Boston, 7 Apr 1813., 1s.(1p.)
  *42M-1952. Presented by the Estate of Samuel Henshaw. Gift of Thomas Barbour and others, June 1942.
- Bulfinch, Charles, 1763-1844. A.L.s.to [Susan (Apthorp) Bulfinch]; London, 17 Sep 1786., 1s.(1p.)
  *59M-207. Gift of H. U. Archives, Feb 1960.
- Bulfinch, Charles, 1763-1844. A.L.s.to Charles Lowell; Washington, 5 Aug 1825., 1s.(2p.)
- Bulfinch, Thomas, 1728-1802. 4 documents (photographs) concerning Bulfinch and his family., 4s.(4p.)
  The originals are owned by Mrs. Charles Bulfinch, Dover, Mass.
- Bulkeley, Morgan Gardner, 1837-1922. A.L.s.to [ ]; Hartford, 2 Jan 1893., 1s.(1p.)
- Bull, Sara Chapman (Thorp) 1850-1911. A.L.s.to [ ] Abbott; Cambridge, 4 Jan 1882., 1s.(2p.)
- Bull, Sara Chapman (Thorp) 1850-1911. A.L.s.to [ ]; Elmwood [n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
- Bull, Sara Chapman (Thorp) 1850-1911. A.L.s.to [ ] Hutton; New York [n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
  Also calling card.
- Bull, Sara Chapman (Thorp) 1850-1911. A.L.s.to [Mrs ] Porter; Cambridge, 13 Oct 1880., 1s.(1p.)
- Bullard, Mr., recipient. Manuscript letter from unidentified correspondent; no place, 1842 March 21., 1s.(1p.)
  Incomplete letter, no signed. Expresses regret that he can not comply.
- Bullock, Alexander Hamilton, 1816-1882. A. signature; Boston,1867., 1s.(1p.)
- Bullard, Laura Curtis A.L.s.to [ ]; Paris, 15 Jun 1887., 1s.(4p.)
- Buller, Charles, 1806-1848. A.signature; London, 4 Dec 1830., 1s. (1p.)
- Buller, Sir Wentworth A.L.s.to [ ]; Moretonhampstead, 20 Oct 1873., 1s.(4p.)
- Bullock, Alexander Hamilton, 1816-1882. A.L.s.to [ ] Greenough; Worcester, 8 Jan 1874., 1s.(1p.)
- Bullock, Rufus Brown, 1834-1907. A. signature; Atlanta, 30 Mar 1871., 1s.(1p.)
- Bullock, Rufus Brown, 1834-1907. A.L.s.to Erastus Brainerd; Atlanta, 4 Oct 1884., 3s.(3p.)
- Bulow, Freidrich Wilhelm, Freitherr von, count of Denneuritz, 1755-1816. MS.D.s.; Milau, 8 Nov 1812., 1s.(2p.)
- Bult, Henry B. A.L.s.to John A. Weisse; New York, 19 May 1886., 1s.(1p.)
  Also a.envelope addressed to Prof. H. A. Taine.
- Bunbury, Sir Henry Edward, 7th bart., 1778-1860. 3 A.L.s.to Messrs.Broom,Harriss Co.:
  - Barton, 8 Mar 1827., 1s.(1p.)
  - Mildenhall, 24 Oct 1816., 1s.(1p.)
  - Suffolk, 9 Sep 1816., 1s.(1p.)
- Bunbury, Henry William, 1750-1811. A.L.s.to [Mrs. Thomas Macklin]; Keswick, 9 Sep 1804., 1s.(1p.)
  Also copy of "A Barber's Shop" with a printed explanation.
- Bunce, Oliver Bell, 1828-1890. A.L.s.to Century Publishing Company; New York, 8 Dec 1885., 1s.(2p.)
- Bundy, McGeorge, 1919- T.L.s. to Nathan Marsh Pusey; Washington, 2 Feb 1965., 1s.(1p.)
  With a T.L.(carbon copy) by Pusey to Claudia Alta (Taylor) Johnson; Cambridge 9 Feb 1965. 1s.(1p.)
  With *64-1105. Gift of Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, Feb 1965.
- Bunn, Alfred, 1796?-1860. A.L.s. to John Murray; [London, n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
  *54M-210. Received gratis, Mar 1955.
- Bunn, William M. 3 A.L.s.to Erastus Brainerd:
  - Philadelphia, 22 Apr 1890., 1s.(1p.)
  - Same, 10 Jan 1917., 1s.(1p.) env.
  - Same, 19 Jan 1917., 1s.(2p.)
- Bunner, Henry Cuyler, 1855-1896. I wish this to carry ... [first line] A.MS.s.; [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
  *44M-311 Gift of Talbot Aldrich, 20 Feb 1945.
- Bunner, Henry Cuyler, 1855-1896. T.L.s. to [ ] Ellsworth; Nutley, 4 Apr [189-?], 1s.(1p.)
- Bunner, Henry Cuyler, 1855-1896. 2 A.L.s.to [Mrs Lawrence] Hutton:
  - [New York] 25 Dec 1885., 1s.(1p.)
  - [Same, n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Bunsen, Christian Karl Josias, freiherr von, 1791-1860. A.L.s. to W. Reichel; Rome, 26 Feb. 1829., 1s.(2p.)
  *45M-181(81) Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Burch, Charles S. T.L.s.to [ ] Gorham; Riverdale on Hudson, 21 Sep 1912., 1s.(1p.)
- Burchard, Samuel Dickinson, 1812-1891. A.L.s.to Edwin Francis Hatfield; New York, 21 Sep 1864., 1s.(1p.)
- Burdett, Sir Francis, 1770-1844. A.L.s. to [ ]; [n.p.] 10 Aug 1834., 1s.(1p.)
  *45M-181(82) Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Burdett, Sir Francis, 1770-1844. A.L.s. to William Nevin [?]; [London, n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
- Burdette, Robert Jones, 1844-1914. A.L.s.to [ ]; Bryn Mawr, 28 May [n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Burdette, Robert Jones, 1844-1914. A.L.s.to Robert Ellis Thompson; West Chester, 15 Jul [n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
  Also a.signature; [n.p.,n.d.] 1s.(1p.)
- Burges, Tristram, 1770-1853. A.L.s. to [ ]; [n.p.] 22 Apr 1845., 1s.(2p.)
- Burgess, Gelett, 1866-1951. 'Goop' cut out for Julia. Hand cut paper dolls; [n.p., n.d.], 1 item 5.5 x 28 cm.
  With annotated envelope.
  *93M-120. Gift of Alice Lovett, no date.
- Burghley, William Cecil, 1st baron, 1520-1598. MS.s.( W. Burghley ); [n.p.] 11 May 1576., 1s.(1p.)
  *51M-133. Purchased from Marvin Sadik, 10 Jan 1952.
- Burghley, William Cecil, 1st baron, 1520-1598. MS.D.s.; [London,15--?], 1s.(1p.)
  Bill of Anthony Conwaye, messenger, endorsed by Burghley.
  *42M-1740. Gift of W. B. O. Field, winter 1942.
- Burgoyne, John, 1722-1792. A.L.s.to Frederick North, 2d earl of Guilford; Boston, 10 Oct 1775., 2s.(8p.)
  Murdock MS 6, n.d.
- Burke, Edmund, 1729-1797. A.L.s. to [David] Garrick; [n.p., ca. 1758], 1s. (2p.).
  With postscript by William Burke.
  Murdock MS 7, n.d.
- Burke, Edmund, 1729-1797. A.L.s. to Stephen Thurston Adey; Beaconsfield, 28 Mar 1788., 1s.(2p.)
- Burke, Edmund, 1729-1797. A.L.s. to Richard Shackleton; [n.p. 5 Jun 1787], 1s.(2p.)
  Norton autographs, n.d.
- Burlingame, Anson, 1820-1870. A.L.s.to Norman Allison Calkins; Boston, 15 Dec [n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
- Burlingame, Anson, 1820-1870. 2 A.L.s.to James Dolliver:
  - Washington, 17 Jan 1860., 1s.(1p.)
  - Same, 19 Feb 1860., 1s.(1p.) env.
    Also engraved calling card.
- Burlingame, Anson, 1820-1870. MS.(by A. B. Johnson ); to [ ]; Washington, 28 Feb 1859., 1s.(1p.)
- Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, 1833-1898. 6 A.L.s. to George Hamilton;1870-1886.
  See Accessions Records, 1942-1943 under *42M-1837 to 1842. All the letters deal with the painting, Pan and Psyche.
  *42M-1837-1842. Presented by the Estate of Grenville L. Winthrop, 30 June 1943.
- Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, 1833-1898. A.L.s.( Ned ) to [John Ruskin]; [n.p., 1872?], 2s.(6p.)
- Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, 1833-1898. A.L.s.( Ned ) to [John Ruskin]; [London, May 1866], 1s.(4p.)
- Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, 1833-1898. A.L.s.( Ned ) to [John Ruskin]; [n.p., 1877-1878?], 1s.(3p.)
- Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, 1833-1898. A.L.s. to [Frederick] Hollyer; [London, n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
  Hollyer was a photographer.
  *62M-302. Purchased with the Wells fund, June 1963.
- Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, 1833-1898. Autograph letter signed to Mrs. G. M. Whitin; West Kensington (London, England),1897 Jan. 23., 1 folder
  Concerns a commissioned painting Burne-Jones was about to send to Mrs. Whitin in Massachusetts.
  *95M-66. Given by David and Shiu-min Block, 1996 May 23.
- [Burnet, Gilbert, bp. of Salisbury, 1643-1715]. MS.; [n.p., 1687]., 5f.(9p.)
- Burnet, William. A.L.s. to Nicholas Low; Second River, 9 Jun 1793., 1s.(3p.)
- Burnett, Frances Hodgson, 1849-1924. Autograph letter signed to Mrs. [Knore?]; New York (N.Y.), undated., 1 folder
- Burnett, Frances Hodgson, 1849-1924. A.L.s. to [ ] Swift[?]; San Remo, [n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
  *45M-181 (83) Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Burnett, Frances Hodgson, 1849-1924. A.L.s.to [ ]; New York, 8 Oct 1907., 1s.(1p.)
- Burney, Andrew Signature on promissory note; Savannah, 11 Dec 1793., 1s.(1p.)
- Burney, Fanny, 1752-1840. A.L.s.to Stephen Allen; Queen's Square, 13 Nov 1773., 1s.(2p.) in 1 folder.
- Burney, Fanny, 1752-1840. A.L.s. to Richard Bentley; [London] 4 Nov 1835., 1s. (2p.) in 1 folder.
  *46M-111. Purchased with the Bemis fund from Maggs Brothers, Cat. 753, 12 Jul 1946.
- Burney, Fanny, 1752-1840. A.L.(unsigned) to Martin Burney; [Chelsea, 13 Dec 1813], 1s.(2p.) in 1 folder.
  Lot 295, A.E.Newton sale.
  *58M-69. Purchased with the Greenough fund from Seven Gables Bookshop, Oct 1958.
- Burney, Fanny, 1752-1840. A.L.(unsigned) to Marianne [ ]; [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(1p.) in 1 folder.
  With original pen and ink sketch by C. D. Sherburn.
- Burney, Fanny, 1752-1840. A.L.(third person) to [ ] Nichols; [London] 23 Jan 1833., 1s.(1p.) in 1 folder.
  *42M-499(3). Gift of Dr. Harris Kennedy, 26 Jan 1943.
- Burney, Fanny, 1752-1840. A.L.s.to Mrs. [Hester Lynch] Thrale; [n.p.] 26 Nov [1780], 1s.(2p.) in 1 folder.
  Relating to Mrs. Thrale's illness.
  Mrs. Thrale was Hester Lynch Piozzi (1741-1821).
  Murdock MS 2, n.d.
- Burney, M. L. A.L.s. to Sarah Orne Jewett; South Berwick, Me., 16 Jun 1880., 1s.(2p.)
- Burnham, Aaron A.receipt s.; [n.p.] 25 Jun 1795., 1s. (1p.)
- Burns, Robert, 1759-1796. A.L.s. to Peter Hill; [n.p., n.d.], 1s.(4p.)
  Contains draft of: Ca' the yowes to the knowes; On seeing Mrs. Kemble in Yarico; on W-- R-- Esquire.
  *45M-181 (85) Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Burns, Robert, 1759-1796. A.L.(latter part wanting) to [Robert] Riddell; [n.p., n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
  *45M-181 (86) Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Burns, Robert, 1759-1796. PHOTOSTATS:
  1. "Epigram"; 2. "A Song.Tune,The last time I came o'er the Moor--"; 3. Letter to Charles Hay encl. poem "On the Death of the Late Lord President"; 4.Note of Hugh Dullop of Dunlop, 16 May 1877, encl.song of Burns's "My Love is like a red, red rose."
- Burns, Robert, 1759-1796. A.L.(s. Sylvander ) to Clarinda; [n.p.] Saturday noon [n.d.], 2s.(2p.) Photostat.
- Burns, Robert, 1759-1796. To Miss Ferrier, inclosing the Elegy on Sir J. H. Blair. A.MS.(unsigned facsimile) poem, 5 stanzas of 4 lines each; [Edinburgh,1787], 1s.(1p.)
- Burns, Robert, 1759-1796. A.L.s.(facsimile) to [Captain] Hamilton; [n.p.] 23 Jan 1795., 1s.(2p.)
  From James T. Fields' library, n.d.
- Burns, Robert, 1759-1796. Sketch - Newyearday - To Mrs. Dunlop. A.MS.(unsigned facsimile); [1791?], 1s.(1p.)
  With printed description of the manuscript poem.
- Burns, Robert, 1759-1796. Song. -- The blue-eyed lass. A.MS.(facsimile); [n.p., n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
  Engraving made in 1834.
  *45M-181 (84) Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Burns, Robert, 1759-1796. [Extract from a ledger in his writing] [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
- Burnside, Ambrose Everett, 1824-1881. A.L.s. to Cyrus Hamlin; Providence, 14 Oct 1866., 1s.(1p.)
- Burnside, Ambrose Everett Autograph, dated March21, 1876
  American brigadier-general.
- Burnside, Ambrose Everett, 1824-1881. General orders no.13. To surgeons of regiments in the coast division. MS.(official copy, unsigned); Annapolis, 29 Dec 1861., 1s.(2p.)
  Regulations for shipboard hygiene.
  Recat. fr. MS Am 670.
  Gift of S. A. Green, 19 Sept 1862.
- Burnside, Ambrose Everett, 1824-1881. A. signature; [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Burr, Aaron Signature on a fragment of a legal document.
- Burr, Aaron New York, October, 1802
  Signature on a contract.
- Burr, Aaron, 1756-1836. A.L.(3d person) to [ ] Blake; [n.p.] 2 Sep 1831., 1s.(1p.)
  Norton Autographs, 15 July 1914
- Burr, Aaron, 1756-1836. A.L.s.to George Bloom; [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Burr, Aaron, 1756-1836. MS.L.s. to Elisha Boudinot; New York, 24 Oct 1786., 1s.(1p.)
- Burr, Aaron, 1756-1836. A.L.s. to Estes Howe; New York, 4 Dec 1829., 2s.(2p.)
  *42M-499(23) Gift of Dr. Harris Kennedy, 26 Jan 1943.
- Burr, Aaron, 1756-1836. A.L.s. to J. M. Hopkins; [n.p.] 23 Jul 1799., 1s.(2p.)
  *42M-1232F. Gift of W. B. O. Field, winter 1942.
- Burr, Aaron, 1756-1836. A.L.s.to Robert Morris
  - New York, 5 Dec 1800., 1s.(2p.)
  - Also signed check to [ ]; New York, 16 Dec 1796., 1s.(1p.)
    Gift of Mrs. Murray A. Potter, 1 July 1930.
- Burr, Aaron, 1756-1836. A.L.s.to Daniel Tompkins; Washington, 12 Dec 1803., 1s.(1p.)
- Burr, Aaron, 1756-1836. MS.agreement, s.; [n.p.] 10 Jul 1828., 1s.(1p.)
- Burr, Aaron, 1756-1836. Printed D.s.; New York, 6 Aug 1796., 1s.(1p.)
  Check drawn on the U.S.B.Bank of Discount and Deposit.
  *60M-54 (4) In memory of E.S. Wallace, 13 Oct 1960.
- Burr, Aaron New York, Oct. 12, 1791
  Facsimile of check drawn by him
  Also a picture of Isaac Roosevelt on the other side.
- Burr, Albert C, 1829- A. signature; Illinois [n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Burr, Frank A, 1843-1894. T.L.s.to [Charles Warren?] Stoddard; Camden, 28 Jan 1893., 1s.(1p.)
- Burr, Jonathan, d. 1842. A.L.s.to Lemuel Shaw; Sandwich, 27 Nov 1798., 1s.(2p.)
  Gift of S. S. Shaw, 1910.
- Burr, Jonathan, d. 1842. A.L.s.to Oakes Shaw; Sandwich, 12 Dec 1797., 1s.(1p.)
- Burrage, William Clarence. 4 letters; 1887
  Item 1 to Fred Holland Day.
  Concerning the Club of odd volumes, Boston.
  With etching signed by John Taylor Arms.
- Burritt, Elihu, 1810-1879. The Dutch farmer and his horse. A.MS.s.; [n.p.,n.d.], 4s.(4p.)
  *42M-1416. Gift of Talbot Aldrich, 7 June 1943.
- Burritt, Elihu, 1810-1879. A.signature, [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Burritt, Elihu, 1810-1879. A.L.s.to [ ] Drew; London, 5 Jun 1850., 1s.(4p.)
  Gift of Charles H. Taylor, 7 June 1935.
- Burritt, Elihu, 1810-1879. A.L.s.to Editor of Once a Week; Birmingham, 25 Mar 1869., 1s.(1p.)
- Burroughs, John, 1837-1921. A.L.s. to [Lloyd Stephens Bryce]; West Park, N.Y., 14 Mar 1892., 1s.(1p.)
  *43M-224. Purchased with the Sheldon fund, 27 Oct 1943.
- Burroughs, John, 1837-1921. A.L.s. to [ ] Kennedy; Boston, 3 Feb 1896., 1s.(1p.)
  *47M-373 (16) Estate of Samuel Henshaw. Gift of Mr. and Mrs. Alfred M. Tozzer,; Mrs. Thomas Barbour, and Miss Gertrude A. Thurston, June 1943.
- Burroughs, John, 1837-1921. A.L.s. to [Edmund Clarence] Stedman; Esopus, N.Y., 16 Aug 1883., 1s.(4p.)
  Imperfect: damaged, affecting text and signature.
- Burroughs, William Seward, 1914-. Who is the third that walks beside you? TS. with A.MS. corrections; [n.p., 1964], 2s.(2p.)
  Composition about T.S. Eliot.
  With T.L.s. to [ ] Tambimuttu; Morocco, 14 Jun 1964. 1s.(1p.) env.
  Purchased with the Wells fund, 15 Dec 1965.
- Burt, Mary Elizabeth, 1850-1918. A.L.s.to [Wendell Phillips Garrison]; Englewood, 31 Oct 1889., 1s.(2p.)
- Burton, Lewis William, bp., 1852- A.L.s.to American Church Almanac and Year Book; Lexington, Kentucky, 28 Oct 1912., 1s.(1p.)
- Burton, Lewis William, bp., 1852- A.L.s.to Daniel E. Hervey; Lexington, Ky., 22 Nov 1912., 1s.(1p.)
- Burton, Lewis William, bp., 1852- A.L.s.to Daniel E. Hervey; Lexington, Ky., Thanksgiving Day 1912., 1s.(1p.)
- Burton, Sir Richard Francis 1821-1890. A.L.s. to John Auldjo; [n.p.] 1 May [18--], 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. MS Eng 37F.
- BURTON, Theodore E.
  Washington, April 21 1902
  Washington, April 4, 1904
  Washington, February 19, 1912
  Washington, January 18, 1916
  New York, May 10, 1916
  Cleveland, May 20, 1916
  All to Erastus Brainard.
- Burton, Theodore Elijah, 1851-1929. Letters to Erastus Brainard:
  - T.L.s.; Cleveland, 22 May 1916., 1s.(1p.)
  - Telegram; same, 6 Jun 1916., 1s.(1p.)
- Burton, William Evans, 1802-1860. A.L.s. to W. W. Ward; Washington, 2 Oct [n.y.], 1s.(1p.)
- Bury, Charlotte (Campbell),Lady,1775-1861. A.L.(3d person) to Edward Scobell; [n.p.] 30 May 1833., 1s.(1p.)
- Bury, Lady Charlotte (Campbell) 1775-1861. A.L.s. to [ ]; London, 4 Jan 1839., 1s.(1p.)
  *75M-16 (1) Gift of Mrs. Donald F. Hyde, 30 July 1975.
- Busby, Thomas, 1755-1838. A.L.(unsigned) to [ ] Birt; London, 2 Aug 1811., 1s.(1p.)
  Enclosing prospectus for new translation of Lucretius, s.
- Busby, Thomas, 1755-1838. MS.copy of agreement for six lectures; [n.p.] 9 Jul 1811., 1s.(2p.)
  Also a signature; [n.p.] 29 Oct 1811. 1s.(1p.)
- Bush, George, 1796-1859. A.L.s.to [ ] Morse; [n.p., 1853?], 1s.(1p.)
- Bushnell, Horace, 1802-1876. A.L.s.to Edwin Percy Whipple; Hartford, 11 Jun 1869., 1s.(2p.)
- Bushnell, Horace, 1802-1876. A.L.s.to [James Thomas Fields?]; Hartford, 18 Nov [18--? ], 1s.(4p.)
- Bussell, Frederick William, 1862- A.L.s. to Anthony Netboy; Wimbledon, 16 Apr 1932., 1s.(2p.)
  *51M-65. Gift of Anthony Netboy, 10 Aug 1951.
- Bussey, Benjamin, A.L.s.to Samuel Thatcher; Boston, 8 Jun 1876., 1s.(2p.)
- Butcher, Samuel Henry, 1850-1910. A.L.s. to [Mrs. C. N.] Lane; Cambridge, 29 Mar 1904., 1s.(1p.)
- Bute, John Patrick Crichton-Stuart, 3d marquis of, 1847-1900. A.signature; [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Butler, Anthony MS.(3d person) letter to W. Brantz; City of Mexico, 6 May 1830., 1s.(1p.)